(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
[博衣こより生誕Live 2026 ゲームソングLive!]
[Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026: Gaming Song Live!]
いくわよ！こっここよりだよ！
Here I go! It's Kokko-Koyori!
せーの！こっこよーです！
Ready, set, go! It's Kokkoyo-!
はーい、始まりました！こよりのセカンドバースデーライブ！
Yes, Koyori's second birthday live has officially started!
オッケー！
Okay!
こよは、なんと、なんと、なんとですね、
Koyo has, somehow, somehow, somehow...
バースデーライブ、超気合入れてるんです！
prepared so much for this birthday live!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！こよりはスケッチ、てへぺろ！
Hooray! Koyori is sketching, tehepero!
はい、こよ、せーの！
Yes, Koyo, ready, set, go!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
研究助手さんたち全員参戦！
All research assistants, join the battle!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよのまわりはうちゅうかん！
Koyo's surroundings are space-like!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよりの助手席はワンダーランド！
Koyori's passenger seat is a wonderland!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよはピンク！
Koyo is pink!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
おーわーりとおもいきや！
Just when you thought it was over...
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
うそなんだよねー！みゃこ！
It's a lie, Myako!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
甘いゲームしよ？
Shall we play a sweet game?
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
オッケー！こっこよーです！
Okay! It's Kokkoyo-!
せーーの！
Ready, set, go!
やったーー！間に合ったーー！
Hooray! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a beverage!
ちなみに苦手はネギです！
By the way, I hate green onions!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！証明完了！Q.E.D.！
Hooray! Proof complete! Q.E.D.!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こっくらくっく、いただきます！
Kokkurakukku, thank you for the food!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お料理のメニューはポトフを作る！
The menu today is making pot-au-feu!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お助手君？うりうりうりうり！
Assistant-kun? *poke poke poke poke*!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こーりゃいきませんね
This is no good, is it?
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お水まわしましょう！
Let's circulate the water!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
おふろのノックは3回よ！
Three knocks on the bath door!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
あー、あいつもよろしくね！
Ah, please say hello to that guy too!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
うーー、おしおき！
Ooh, punishment!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
やったーー！間に合ったーー！
Hooray! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a beverage!
ちなみに苦手はネギです！
By the way, I hate green onions!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！
Hooray!
私の戦闘力、54万です！
My battle power is 540,000!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お寿司はサーモンがナンバーワンです！
Salmon is the number one sushi!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お仕事お疲れ様、お助手様！
Good job with your work, Mr. Assistant!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
たけのこ派です！きのこはウソ！
I'm Team Takenoko! Kinoko is a lie!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
あー、マカロン15、15！
Ah, macarons, 15, 15!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
シャンプーは飲み物ではありません！
Shampoo is not a beverage!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
ぽんこつなんかじゃ、ありません！
I am not a klutz!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
しっぽもふって、おねだり！
Wagging my tail and begging!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
みんなの応援が必要だよ！
I need everyone's support!
右手ーーー！
Right hand---!
やったーー！間に合ったーー！
Hooray! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a beverage!
ちなみに苦手はネギです！
By the way, I hate green onions!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！
Hooray!
せーの！こっこよー！
Ready, set, go! It's Kokkoyo-!
いくわよ！こっここよりだよー！
Here I go! It's Kokko-Koyori!
せーの！こっこよーです！
Ready, set, go! It's Kokkoyo-!
はーい、始まりました！こよりのセカンドバースデーライブ！
Yes, Koyori's second birthday live has officially started!
オッケー！
Okay!
こよは、なんと、なんと、なんとですね、
Koyo has, somehow, somehow, somehow...
バースデーライブ、超気合入れてるんです！
prepared so much for this birthday live!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！こよりはスケッチ、てへぺろ！
Hooray! Koyori is sketching, tehepero!
はい、こよ、せーの！
Yes, Koyo, ready, set, go!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
研究助手さんたち全員参戦！
All research assistants, join the battle!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよのまわりはうちゅうかん！
Koyo's surroundings are space-like!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよりの助手席はワンダーランド！
Koyori's passenger seat is a wonderland!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こよはピンク！
Koyo is pink!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
おーわーりとおもいきや！
Just when you thought it was over...
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
うそなんだよねー！みゃこ！
It's a lie, Myako!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
甘いゲームしよ？
Shall we play a sweet game?
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
オッケー！こっこよーです！
Okay! It's Kokkoyo-!
せーーの！
Ready, set, go!
やったーー！間に合ったーー！
Hooray! I made it in time!
マヨネーズは飲み物です！
Mayonnaise is a beverage!
ちなみに苦手はネギです！
By the way, I hate green onions!
お肉、全缶、冷凍うどんは常備してます、どうですか？
I've stocked up on meat, all canned food, and frozen udon. How's that?
やったー！証明完了！Q.E.D.！
Hooray! Proof complete! Q.E.D.!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こっくらくっく、いただきます！
Kokkurakukku, thank you for the food!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お料理のメニューはポトフを作る！
The menu today is making pot-au-feu!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お助手君？うりうりうりうり！
Assistant-kun? *poke poke poke poke*!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
こーりゃいきませんね
This is no good, is it?
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
お水まわしましょう！
Let's circulate the water!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
おふろのノックは3回よ！
Three knocks on the bath door!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
あー、あいつもよろしくね！
Ah, please say hello to that guy too!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
うーー、おしおき！
Ooh, punishment!
こよりはマヨネーズで回復した！
Koyori recovered with Mayonnaise!
助手くんが仲間になった！
Assistant-kun joined the party!
AIこよりが仲間になった！
AI Koyori joined the party!
もふこよが仲間になった！
Mofukoyo joined the party!
へい！ カロスを照らすあの朝日のように
Hey! Like that morning sun lighting up Kalos...
（ニトロチャージ熱く行こうぜ）
(Let's go hot with a Nitro Charge!)
さあ！進もうぜ いつでも準備はOK
Come on! Let's go, we're always ready
（型破り 変幻自在で）
(With Mold Breaker and Protean)
重なり合う想いがシンクロして
Our overlapping feelings synchronize,
決して消えない絆になるから
becoming a bond that will never fade.
どこまでも強くなれる
We can become stronger, no matter how far,
俺たちなら
as long as it's us!
いくぜ！！ 激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go!! A fiercely burning battle!
いくぜ！！ ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go!! A crisis is a chance!
いこうぜ！！ 起死回生
Let's go!! A miraculous recovery!
絶対に諦めない
We will absolutely never give up!
俺たちは諦めない
We won't give up!
へい！たとえばどんな壁が道を塞いだって
Hey! No matter what kind of wall blocks our way...
（いつでも当たって砕けろで）
(We'll always go for broke!)
さあ！この手で勝利の星を掴むんだ
Come on! Let's grab the star of victory with our hands...
（折れない不屈の心で）
(with an unbreakable, indomitable heart!)
俺たちはいつでもどんな時でも
We are always, no matter when,
同じ心で繋がっているから
connected with the same heart.
何度でも立ち上がるぜ
So we will rise up again and again,
お前となら
as long as I'm with you!
いくぜ！！ 手強いライバルたち
Let's go!! Against tough rivals!
いくぜ！！ 決めろ一撃必殺
Let's go!! Land a one-hit KO!
いこうぜ！！ 負けられない
Let's go!! We cannot lose,
想いがここにあるから
because our feelings are right here,
夢が俺たちにはあるから
and we have our dreams!
博衣こより生誕ライブ2026！見に来てくれてありがとう！
Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026! Thank you all for coming to watch!
神ゲーたちの神ゲームソングいっぱい詰め込んでるので、最後まで楽しんでいってね！
I've packed this with tons of god-tier songs from god-tier games, so please enjoy it until the end!
いくぜ！！ 勝ちも負ける痛みも
Let's go!! Both victory and the pain of defeat...
いくぜ！！ なんでも分け合える
Let's go!! We can share anything!
いこうぜ！！ 仲間がいる
Let's go!! We have our friends.
俺たちは一人じゃない
We are not alone!
いくぜ！！ 激しく燃えるバトル
Let's go!! A fiercely burning battle!
いくぜ！！ ピンチはチャンスだぜ
Let's go!! A crisis is a chance!
いこうぜ！！ 起死回生
Let's go!! A miraculous recovery!
絶対に諦めない
We will absolutely never give up!
いくぜ！！ 譲れない夢がある GO!
Let's go!! There is a dream we can't yield!
いくぜ！！ 必ずゲットだぜ
Let's go!! We will definitely catch 'em all!
いこうぜ！！ 手を伸ばして
Let's go!! Reach out your hand...
いつか描いた未来へ
toward the future we once drew,
誰も知らない次元まで
to a dimension nobody knows of!
さあ！上げてくぜ 100万ボルト GO!
Come on! Let's turn it up to a million volts!
そう！立ち向かって共に行こうぜ
Yes! Stand up and let's go together...
見たこともない dream の向こうまで
to the other side of a dream we've never seen!
はーい！みんな、こんこよー！
Haaay! Everyone, Konkoyo!
ホロライブ6期生、holoXの頭脳、博衣こよりだよー！
I'm Hakui Koyori, a member of Hololive's 6th Gen and the brain of holoX!
改めて今日は、博衣こより生誕ライブ2026にお越しいただき、ありがとうございます！
Once again, thank you so much for coming to Hakui Koyori Birthday Live 2026 today!
コメントもいっぱいありがとう！イェーイ！かっこいい？見えてるよ、ありがとう！
Thank you so much for all the comments too! Yay! Do I look cool? I see you, thank you!
ということで、ライブの感想やスクショはハッシュタグ「#博衣こより生誕ライブ2026」をつけて、たくさんポストしてください！
And with that, please post your impressions and screenshots of the show with the hashtag #HakuiKoyoriBirthdayLive2026!
目指せ！トレンド入り！よろしくなー！
Aiming to trend! Let's make it happen!
はい！ということで、ちょっと息が整ってないですけど、
Alright! So, I'm a bit out of breath, but...
さて、今年の生誕祭ライブ、テーマは『ゲームソングライブ』です！
Now, the theme of this year's Birthday Live is "Game Song Live"!
これまでたくさんやってきた、実況配信で一緒に遊んできた思い出のゲームや、
I've packed in songs from memorable games we've played together in my many game streams,
こよが大好きゲーム関連の楽曲を、たくさん詰め込みました！
and game-related songs that I absolutely love!
最後まで全力で楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy it with all your might until the very end!
ということで、1曲目は大好きなポケモンの『XYZ』を歌わせていただきました。ね！
So, for the first song, I sang my beloved Pokemon song "XYZ." Right?
じゅしゅくん、
Josh-kun...
「俺はこいつと旅に出る」っていうことです。はい。
It means "I'm going on a journey with this guy." Yes.
XYZ、予想もみんなにたくさんしてもらってたんですけど、
Many of you tried to guess my setlist, including "XYZ"...
ポケモンの予想は結構多かったけど、XYZを当てられた人は結構少なかったです。
And while many guessed Pokemon songs, very few guessed "XYZ" specifically.
当たった君、おめでとう！
Congratulations to those who got it right!
この曲は、Z-Aの発売になったっていうのもあるんですけど、歌詞がめっちゃ良くて、実はこよりにもぴったりな曲なので、選びました！
I chose this song because of the "Legends: Z-A" announcement, but also because the lyrics are amazing and fit me perfectly!
さあ、この後も、自分の予想が当たってるかなって、ドキドキしながら楽しんでいってください！
I hope you'll continue to enjoy the show, excited to see if your other guesses are correct!
新3Dお披露目もあるからね！絶対に最後まで見てってね！
We also have a new 3D outfit reveal coming up! Make sure to watch until the very end!
それでは、そろそろ次の曲。
Well then, it's about time for the next song.
ゲームの世界へ、どうぞ！
Welcome to the game world!
気がついたら
I noticed
同じ面ばかりプレイ
I'm playing the same level over and over
そしていつも同じ場所で死ぬ
And I always die in the same spot
あきらめずに
I don't give up,
消える足場に挑戦するけど
I challenge the vanishing platforms
すぐに下に落ちるよ
But I fall down immediately
アイテム2号があれば
If I have Item 2,
楽に 向こうの岸までつくけど
I can easily reach the other side
何回やっても
But no matter how many times I try
No matter how many times I try
何回やっても 何回やっても
No matter how many times I try, no matter how many times I try,
エアーマンが倒せないよ
I can't defeat Airman.
あの竜巻何回やっても避けれない
I can't avoid that tornado no matter how many times I try.
うしろに回って撃ち続けても
Even if I go behind him and keep shooting,
いずれは風に飛ばされる
I'll eventually get blown away by the wind.
タイム連打も試してみたけど
I tried rapid-firing the pause button too,
竜巻相手じゃ意味が無い
But it's meaningless against the tornado!
だから次は絶対勝つために
So, to make sure I win next time,
僕はE缶だけは最後までとっておく
I'll save my E-tank until the very end.
倒せないよ
I can't defeat him...
ロボのテーマ
[On-Screen: Robo's Theme]
カエルのテーマ
[On-Screen: Frog's Theme]
Melodies Of Life
[On-Screen: Melodies Of Life]
あてもなく 彷徨っていた
I wandered aimlessly,
手がかりもなく探し続けた
Searching endlessly without any clues.
あなたがくれた思い出を
Turning the memories you gave me...
心を癒す歌にして
...into a song that heals my heart.
約束もすることもなく
Without making promises,
交わす言葉も決めたりもせず
Without even deciding on words to say,
抱きしめ、そして確かめた
We held each other close, and made certain
日々は二度と帰らぬ
That those days will never return.
記憶の中の手を振るあなたは
You, waving your hand in my memories...
わたしの名を呼ぶことができるの？
Are you able to call out my name?
あふれるその涙を
Turn those overflowing tears...
輝く夢に変えて
...into a shining dream.
いのちはつづく
Life goes on,
夜を越え
Crossing over the night,
疑うことのない明日へとつづく
Continuing on toward an indubitable tomorrow.
飛ぶ鳥の向こうの空へ
To the sky beyond the flying birds,
いくつの記憶預けただろう
How many memories have we entrusted?
儚い希望も夢も
Fleeting hopes and dreams alike,
届かぬ場所に忘れて
Forgotten in an unreachable place.
めぐり逢うのは偶然と言えるの？
Can we say our meeting was just a coincidence?
別れる時が必ず来るのに
Even though the time to part will surely come...
消えゆく運命でも
Even if it is a fleeting destiny,
君が生きている限り
As long as you are alive...
いのちはつづく
Life goes on,
永遠に
Eternally,
その力の限りどこまでも
To wherever, as long as that strength lasts.
わたしが死のうとも
Even if I should die,
君が生きている限り
As long as you are alive...
いのちはつづく
Life goes on,
永遠に
Eternally,
その力の限り
As long as that strength lasts,
どこまでもつづく
It will continue forever.
きみの瞳に映る
What color am I...
わたしは何色ですか
...in your eyes?
赤深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep red,
渡そう 陽の光を
I will give you the sunlight.
Ah...
悲しみが溢れ
Overflowing with sadness,
瞼閉じました
I closed my eyelids.
こぼれた滴は
The spilled teardrops
心に沁みゆく
seep into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The spreading waves
弱く交えます
are weakly mingled.
とどけしゆりかご
Delivered cradle,
眠りをさそう
inviting sleep.
夢になつかし
Searching for nostalgic images
面影をさがす
in my dreams.
手を伸ばし強く
Stretching out my hand, strongly
抱きしめたくなる
I want to hold you tight...
きみの瞳に映る
What color am I...
わたしは何色ですか
...in your eyes?
藍深き望むなら
If you wish for a deep indigo,
渡そう高き空を
I will give you the high sky.
不安定な神様 繰り返す出会いと別れ
An unstable god, repeating meetings and partings.
また会える その日まで 解きかける旅人
Until the day we meet again, a traveler solving riddles.
あなたが泣いている 流る涙の雨
You are crying, a rain of flowing tears.
泣くなとは言わない 心悲しくて
I won't tell you not to cry, with a sad heart.
生きて行けるもの 何かを背負いながら
Living on, while carrying something,
見えない鎖に繋がれている
we are bound by invisible chains.
どれほど救われただろう あどけない笑顔に
How much I must have been saved by that innocent smile.
失くしたくはない
I don't want to lose it.
不安定な神様 繰り返す哀哀
An unstable god, repeating sorrow after sorrow.
生まれてそして死んでゆく宿命
The destiny of being born and then dying.
かけ違えた世界で 繰り返す出会いと別れ
In a mismatched world, repeating meetings and partings.
また会える その日まで 解きかける旅人
Until the day we meet again, a traveler solving riddles.
偽りのない心 黒く染めゆきながら
While a heart with no lies is dyed in black,
抑えられなくて 解き放たれてる
unable to suppress it, it's unleashed.
何回名を呼んだだろう あどけない笑顔は
How many times have I called your name? That innocent smile...
もうどこにもない
...is nowhere to be found anymore.
不安定な神様
An unstable god...
引き継いだ夢と愛を
The dreams and love we inherited,
育てて守りゆく宿命
It is our destiny to nurture and protect them.
駆け違えた世界で
In a mismatched world,
探す旅 引き裂かれても
A journey of searching, even if we are torn apart.
また会える と信じて
Believing we will meet again,
時駆ける旅人
A traveler crossing time.
不安定な神様
An unstable god,
繰り返す過去と未来
Repeating past and future,
生まれ そして死んで行く運命
Born, and then a destiny to die.
駆け違えた世界で
In a mismatched world,
繰り返す出会いと別れ
Repeated encounters and partings,
また会える その日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
A traveler crossing time.
また会える その日まで
Until the day we can meet again,
時駆ける旅人
A traveler crossing time.
はい！ということで！Suaraさんにお越しいただき、一緒に歌わせていただきました！
Alright, so! Suara-san has joined us, and we got to sing together!
Suaraさん、自己紹介をいただいてもよろしいでしょうか？
Suara-san, would you please introduce yourself?
はい、Suaraです。えー、『うたわれるもの』シリーズの主題歌をたくさん歌っている者です。
Hi, I'm Suara. Um, I'm the one who sings many of the theme songs for the "Utawarerumono" series.
はい！ようこそー！
Yes! Welcome!
こよりちゃん。
Koyori-chan.
そうなんです。えー、実はですね、『うたわれるもの』というゲーム、えー、昨年約3ヶ月間かけてシリーズの三部作を実況プレイさせていただいたんですけれども、
Yes, that's right. Actually, last year I did a gameplay stream of the "Utawarerumono" trilogy over about three months, but...
ま、その『うたわれるもの』本当に曲がめちゃくちゃいいの、良いのですが、その歌をほぼ全てSuaraさんが歌っていらっしゃるという、
Well, "Utawarerumono" really has incredibly great music, but almost all of those songs are sung by Suara-san,
のです！
you see!
はい。（笑）
Yes. (laughs)
もう、もう耳が今日、本当に幸せで。
My ears are just so, so happy today.
いや、こちらこそですよ、本当に。
No, same here, really.
もう、とっても恐縮な恐れ多い状態なんですけれども、ありがとうございます、本当に。
I'm in a very humbled, awestruck state, but thank you so much, really.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
はい。Suaraさんには、実は4周年の時に逆凸でメッセージも頂戴しておりまして、
Yes. Actually, during my 4th anniversary, Suara-san left a message during a reverse-call stream,
その時に「いつか一緒に歌いたい」というのをこよりも結構熱烈なラブコールをさせていただいていたんですけれども、
and at that time, I sent quite a passionate love call saying, "I want to sing together someday,"
その思いを本日叶えることができました！
and today I was able to make that wish come true!
わーい！
Yay!
え、あの、ちょっと質問が何個かあるんですけれども。
Um, I actually have a few questions.
はい。
Yes.
実は、あの『うたわれるもの』の実況していただいた時に、最終回でSuaraさんがコメントしてくださいまして。
Actually, when I was streaming "Utawarerumono", Suara-san commented on the final episode.
はい。あの、こよりの実況をちょっとご覧くださったと思うんですけれども、
Yes. I believe you watched some of my streams,
はい、はい。
Yes, yes.
そうなんです。あの、見られますか？実況とかって普段。
Right. Do you usually watch gameplay streams?
いや、ちょっと、実はですね、初めて見させていただいて。
Well, to be honest, it was my first time watching one.
そうなんです、あの、まぁ、えー、アクアプラスのね、スタッフの方とかも、
That's right, um, well, the staff at Aquaplus...
「こよりさんというね、『うたわれる』配信してるよ」って言って、情報は聞いていたんですよね。
...told me, "Koyori-san is doing an 'Utawareru' stream," so I had heard about it.
で、私のライブに来てくれるファンの方たちからも、あの、聞いてたんですよ。「ぜひ見てみてください」って。
And my fans who come to my live shows also told me about it, saying, "You should definitely watch it."
それで、あの、見させていただいたっていうのが、あの最終回だったんですけれども、
So, the stream I happened to watch was the final episode, but...
そうだったんですね！恐縮です、本当に。
I see! I'm so honored, really.
いえいえ、もうすごい、あの、本当に、こう、こよりさんの『うたわれるもの』への愛がすごい溢れてて。
No, no, it was amazing. Truly, your love for "Utawarerumono" was overflowing.
本当に見てて、もう最後までずっと、
Watching it, I stayed until the very end...
見させていただいて。
and watched it all.
で、「あ、コメント送りたいな」って、
Then I thought, "Ah, I want to send a comment," but...
あ、でも、もう早くしないと終わっちゃうって思いながら、
also, "I have to do it quickly or it'll end!"
で、あの、同じ部屋に、あの、私の息子がいたんですけれども。
And, my son was in the same room with me.
お、はい！
Oh, yes!
息子さんに！
With your son!
息子に、「あの、コメントちょっと送ってみていいと思う？」って言って、
I asked my son, "Do you think it's okay if I send a comment?"
はい、はい。
Yes, yes.
聞いたら、「いいんじゃない？」って言って。
And he said, "Why not?"
いい息子さんだ！
What a great son!
それで、もう本当に震える手でコメントを打って。で、もう、「あ、早く、もうエンターキーをこう、」
So with really trembling hands, I typed the comment, and thought, "Ah, quickly, the Enter key..." like that,
はい、それでドキドキしながら、あのー送らせていただいたら、ね、あの、コメント気付いてくださって...
Yes, so I was really nervous when I sent it, but then you noticed my comment...
もう、とっても嬉しかったです！こよりもですし、見てた助手くんたちもものすごく嬉しくて、やっぱり、あの、見ていただけるっていうのが...
I was so happy! Both me and the Joshu-kuns watching were incredibly happy. Having you watch us...
Suaraさんとか、あの、AQUAPLUSさんもそうですし...
...Suara-san, and AQUAPLUS too...
その公式の皆さんに、ご覧いただけるって、本当に嬉しく恐縮なことなので、もう幸せでございました！ありがとうございました！
...having official people watch us is truly such a joyful and humbling thing, I was so happy! Thank you so much!
もう、すごい楽しくて、見入っちゃいました！本当に！
It was so fun that I was totally glued to the screen! Truly!
すごい長時間、ゲームをされているのが凄いなと思って、本当に。
I thought it was amazing how you played for such a long time, really.
はい、もう、その日の夜も歌枠も聞かせていただいたり...
Yes, and I even listened to your singing stream that night too...
すごい体力だなって、思いながら。
...thinking, "What amazing stamina!"
でも、楽しんでるのはね、うたわれるものが本当に素晴らしい作品だったから、ですので...
But I enjoyed it because "Utawarerumono" is truly such a wonderful series...
その、うたわれるものとずっとお付き合いしていらっしゃるSuaraさんですけれども、推しキャラとかっていらっしゃるんですか？
So, you've been involved with "Utawarerumono" for a long time, Suara-san... Do you have a favorite character?
推しキャラですか？推しキャラはやっぱりちょっと、エルルゥってことに...
My favorite character? My favorite would have to be Eruruu...
ってことにしとかないと、ちょっとフォークで刺されるかもしれない...
...I have to say that, otherwise I might get stabbed with a fork...
あはは！あれ？もしかして...
Ahaha! Wait, by any chance...
仲が良い、そう、中の人の柚木涼香さんととっても仲良くさせていただいてて。
...are you close with her voice actress, Ryoka Yuzuki-san? Yes, we are very close friends.
本当に、アニメの放送の時からですね、2006年からずっと仲良くさせていただいてるっていう...
Really, ever since the anime broadcast back in 2006, we've been close all this time...
おぉー！20年！そうですね、20年。ふふふ。はい。
Oh! Almost 20 years! That's right, 20 years. Haha. Yes.
それはエルルゥ推し。ですね！ということで、エルルゥ推しということでお願いします。
So I'm an Eruruu fan. Definitely! So let's go with Eruruu being my favorite character, please.
こよりは、もう、アルルゥが大好きなので、エルルゥ・アルルゥで、姉妹で！姉妹で！はい。嬉しいです！
Koyori absolutely loves Aruruu, so between Eruruu and Aruruu, we have the sisters! The sisters! Yes. I'm so happy!
はい、ということで、もっともっとお話したいんですけれども、お時間が来てしまいまして。もう本当に、今日は一緒に歌っていただきありがとうございました！
All right, and with that, I'd love to talk even more, but we've run out of time. Really, thank you so much for singing with me today!
ありがとうございました！こよりさんの本当に柔らかい、優しい、ね、温かい声にこう包まれながら、私も一緒に歌えて本当に幸せでした。
Thank you so much! Being enveloped by your truly soft, gentle, and warm voice, Koyori-san, singing together with you made me really happy.
恐縮でございます！ありがとうございます！
I'm so honored! Thank you so much!
また是非いろいろご一緒させていただく機会があれば嬉しいです！是非是非、よろしくお願いします！
I'd be absolutely thrilled if we could do something together again in the future! Definitely, I'd love to!
ありがとうございます！ということで、Suaraさんでしたー！ありがとうございましたー！ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much! And with that, our guest was Suara-san! Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
こよりのリズムラボ
[Koyori's Rhythm Lab]
9th リミックス
[9th Remix]
やがて女はきれいになるだろう
Eventually, a woman will become beautiful
オッケー！ドンマイ！
Okay! Don't mind!
Much times Much だいスキ だいスキ だいスキ
Much times, I love you, love you, love you
みっつ
Three
突然に降ってきた 私の人生
Suddenly, it dropped into my life
よっしゃ！
Alright!
本当の自分に出逢えた
I met my true self
よっしゃ！
Alright!
あのダンスがセクシー 私は女の子
That dance is sexy, I'm a girl
ダンスしてクレイジー 生まれたて素敵よ
Dance and go crazy, newly born and wonderful
輝きたい 愛されたい
I want to shine, I want to be loved
歴史が放っておかない
History won't leave me alone
よっしゃ！
Alright!
華やかな人生 生きたい
I want to live a glamorous life
悲しい歌流れる
A sad song plays
街の中歩く
Walking through the town
涙乾き流れてゆく
Tears dry and flow away
涙乾き流れてゆくのは
Tears drying and flowing away is...
どうしてなんだろう
I wonder why
よっしゃ！
Alright!
ワン・ツー・スリー・フォー
One, two, three, four
て・ゆ・う・て・ま・す・が
So they say...
デカい夢抱きしめて
Embracing a huge dream
誰も信じられなくちゃ
If you can't believe in anyone
期待だけなきゃいい
If only there weren't expectations
ワン・ツー・スリー・フォー
One, two, three, four
て・ゆ・う・て・ま・す・が
So they say...
だからもっと恋して
So love even more
胸を締め付けられて
With my chest tightening
周りが見えなくなってみたい
I want to try losing sight of my surroundings
みっつ
Three
だいスキ！だいスキ！だいスキ！
I love you! I love you! I love you!
こっち見て
Look at me
Much times Much だいスキ だいスキ だいスキ
Much times, I love you, love you, love you
みっつ
Three
愛♥スクリーム！
[Song: Love Scream!]
教えてもっとあなたのこと
Tell me more about you.
Tell me, more, more, more! Tell me, more, more, more!
聞かせてもっとあなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice.
Let me hear, more, more, more! Let me hear, more, more, more!
こんなドキドキ、もう避けらんない！
I can't avoid this pounding heart anymore!
Oh, all I need you! Oh, all I need you!
友達は卒業、運命の私 見つけてほしいの
I want to graduate from being friends and have you find the destined me.
One! 勇気を出して
One! Have some courage.
Two! 見つめる作戦
Two! Staring strategy.
Three! 目と目が合えば
Three! If our eyes meet...
Four! 止められない！
Four! I can't stop!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! この恋、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this love, this affection...
Melt, melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt!
ねぇねぇねぇ、気づいて my darling!
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
届け、大好き！
Deliver my "I love you"!
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！ (Okay!)
Scream, ice cream! (Okay!)
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！
Scream, ice cream!
こよりちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
マヨネーズ！よりも、あなた！
Mayonnaise! More than that, you!
あずきちゃん！
Azuki-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
こしあん、つぶあん、よりも、あなた！
Smooth, chunky red bean paste... more than that, you!
らみぃちゃん！
Lamy-chan!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
お酒よりも、あなた！
More than alcohol, you!
みんなー！
Everyone!
はーい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん、大好き、こ・よ・り！
Of course, we love Ko-yo-ri!
止められない！
I can't stop!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! この恋、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this love, this affection...
Melt, melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt!
ねぇねぇねぇ、気づいて my darling!
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
届け、大好き！
Deliver my "I love you"!
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！ (Okay!)
Scream, ice cream! (Okay!)
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！
Scream, ice cream!
お願い、見つけて my darling!
Please find me, my darling!
お願い、気づいて my darling!
Please notice me, my darling!
One! 勇気を出して
One! Have some courage.
Two! 近づく作戦
Two! Strategy to get closer.
Three! 手と手が触れて
Three! If our hands touch...
Four! 止められない！
Four! I can't stop!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! この恋、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this love, this affection...
Melt, melty とけちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm going to melt!
ねぇねぇねぇ、気づいて my darling!
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling!
それは、あなた！
That is you!
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！ (Okay!)
Scream, ice cream! (Okay!)
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！
Scream, ice cream!
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！ (Okay!)
Scream, ice cream! (Okay!)
アイスクリーム、スクリーム、叫びましょう
Ice cream, scream, let's shout!
スクリーム、アイスクリーム！
Scream, ice cream!
La la la...
もう何十回も 何百回も 何千回も
Already dozens, hundreds, thousands of times...
澄む空見上げて
Looking up at the clear sky,
たどり着いた場所が
The place we finally arrived at...
運命のダイヤモンド
...is the diamond of destiny.
何千回も 何万回も
Thousands, tens of thousands of times,
涙流した君へ
To you, who shed so many tears,
ねえ諦められたことはあったっけ
Hey, did we ever have a reason to give up?
あこがれは限界の彼方
My adoration lies beyond the limits,
もういらないよ よそ見も
I don't need to look away anymore.
ただ守るなんて
Just defending...
もったいないでしょ
...is such a waste, isn't it?
それぞれの物語
Our respective stories...
交差する瞬間を
The moment they intersect,
見つめる日々は
The days we watch over them...
放った夢だけ
Only the dreams we let loose,
大きな声出して
Shouting out loud,
はじけそうなきらめきも
And the sparkles that seem about to burst,
消えることなく
Without ever fading away,
どこまででも
No matter how far...
世界の向こうに届け
Reach to the other side of the world!
終わることのない
Endless...
この胸の衝動は
...impulse in this chest,
どうしたって どうしても
No matter what, no matter how,
もう夢を呼んでいたから
Because it was already calling out to my dreams!
その先へと
Towards what lies beyond,
走り続ける
I'll keep on running,
次へ 次へ
To the next, and the next!
もう育ってた
I had already grown up,
中途半端な
Holding onto this half-hearted...
悔しさ抱えて
...frustration,
立ち尽くしていた
Standing still,
手を振った
I waved my hand...
よかったね、と
...and said, "I'm glad."
廊下の隅見下ろす 掃除の途中
Looking down from the corner of the hallway, in the middle of cleaning,
おかしなものだと 思う
I think it's strange.
あたしの中の時は止まってるのに
Even though time inside me has stopped,
違う日々を生きてるように
it feels like I'm living in different days.
埃は雪のように降り積む
The dust accumulates like snow.
待ってる気がした
I felt like I was waiting...
呼んでる気がしたんだ
...I felt like someone was calling me.
震えだす今この時が
And now, this trembling moment...
見つけた気がした
...I felt like I found it.
失われた記憶が呼び覚ました
The lost memories awakened...
物語
...the story...
永遠の
...of eternity...
その終わり
...and its end.
いつの間にか駆けだしてた
Before I knew it, I started running,
あなたに手を引かれてた
with my hand being pulled by you.
昨日は遠く 明日はすぐ
Yesterday is far away, tomorrow is near...
そんな当たり前に
...at such an ordinary thing...
昨日は遠く
Yesterday is far away...
明日はすぐ
...tomorrow is near.
そんな当たり前に
At such an ordinary thing...
心が踊った
...my heart danced.
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I felt it.
震えだす今この胸で
Now, my heart starts to tremble.
もう来る気がした
I felt like it was coming already,
幾千の朝を越え 新しい陽が
crossing thousands of mornings, a new light...
待ってる気がした
...I felt like it was waiting,
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling me.
震えてるこの魂が
This trembling soul of mine...
見つけた気がした
...felt like it found...
幾億の夢のように消え去れる日を
...the day when I can fade away like billions of dreams.
見送った
I watched it go...
手を振った
...and waved my hand...
ありがとう、と
...saying, "Thank you."
ぽつり灯り 管制塔
A solitary light in the control tower,
砂嵐の向こうへ
towards the other side of the sandstorm.
祈るように 綴った
As if praying, I wrote down
これからのこと
about the things to come.
ラジオネーム 匿名希望
Radio name: Anonymous Hope.
お便り届いてますか？
Has my letter reached you?
この世界がいつからか
Since when did this world...
まるで他人事のように
...become like someone else's affair?
やけに静かなので
Because it is so awfully quiet,
不安になったのです
I became anxious.
思い出したのです
I just remembered...
人知れず 口をつぐんだまま
keeping my mouth shut, unbeknownst to anyone,
終われないのです
I cannot let it end.
それは嫌なのです
I don't want that.
夢ってもっと
Dreams used to be...
わがままだったでしょう
...much more selfish, weren't they?
応えてよ
Answer me,
笑ってよ
laugh,
気づいてよ
notice me.
此処に居るのに
Even though I'm right here,
意地悪だな
you are so mean.
誰にも届かない光を
To a light that reaches no one,
どうしたら 伝えられるのでしょう
how can I ever convey it?
どうしても 伝えたいよ
I want to convey it, no matter what.
ラジオネーム、匿名希望。
Radio name: Anonymous.
意気地無しなのでしょうか。
Am I a coward?
それとも、この世界には、
Or in this world...
私はお邪魔でしょうか。
...am I an intruder?
だとしたって綴るよ。
Even so, I'll write it down.
みっともなく叫ぶよ。
I'll scream ungracefully.
振られたって好きだよ。
Even if I'm rejected, I love you.
いいでしょ。
That's fine, right?
楽しかったよね。
It was fun, wasn't it?
悔しかったよね。
It was frustrating, wasn't it?
もう独り言は嫌だ。
I'm tired of talking to myself.
「待たせちゃったかな」
"Did I keep you waiting?"
「別に待ってないよ」
"I wasn't really waiting."
夢と呼んだそれも僕たちだけ。
The thing we called a dream was only ours.
もういいかい。
Are you ready yet?
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ。
Answer me, smile at me, notice me.
此処に居るのにな。
Even though I'm right here.
意地悪だな。
You're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を、
A light that reaches no one...
ぼくだけは光と呼び続ける。
...I alone will keep calling it light.
真夜中、管制塔から。
In the middle of the night, from the control tower,
世界を明かしてやる。
I will light up the world.
特報
[Title: Special News]
管制塔より
[Title: From the Control Tower]
応えてよ、笑ってよ、気付いてよ。
Answer me, smile at me, notice me.
此処に居るのにな。
Even though I'm right here.
意地悪だな。
You're so mean.
誰にも届かない光を、
A light that reaches no one...
どうして堪えられるのでしょう。
...how can you endure it?
どうして伝えたいよ。
Why? I want to convey it to you.
ライブ終了直後 プレミア公開
[Title: Premiering right after the live stream concludes]
というわけで！新曲のお披露目！
And so! The new song reveal!
フルアニメーションMV公開の告知、新3Dのお披露目！
The full animation MV announcement, and my new 3D model reveal!
３個どどん！とまとめてやらせていただきましたー！いぇーい！
I got to do all three at once! Yay!
情報量多かったけど、追いついてるかなー？
There was a lot of info, but are you keeping up?
はい、ちょっとね新3Dが可愛すぎて気になっちゃうと思うんですけど、
Yes, I know you might be distracted because the new 3D is too cute...
まずはオリ曲の話からさせてください！
...but please let me talk about my original song first!
お披露目させていただいたのは新曲『管制塔より』！
The song I revealed was my new song, "From the Control Tower"!
はい！え、ついにあの堀江晶太さんに書き下ろしていただきました！
Yes! It was written for me by Shota Horie!
みんな、どうだったー？エモい？良かったー！
How was it, everyone? Was it emotional? I'm so glad!
はい、そしてですね、今ちょっと映像も流して、すごい追いついてくれててめっちゃ嬉しいんですけど、
Yes, and I'm so happy that you guys are catching up while we play the video,
このライブ終了直後にフルアニメーションMVがプレミア公開されます！
...the full animation MV will premiere right after this live stream ends!
多分もう、あのマネちゃんがポチッとしてくれてると思います！
My manager has probably already clicked the button to set it up!
世界観がめちゃくちゃこだわられている映像作品になっているので、
It's a visual piece with a highly detailed worldview,
何回も見て、聴いて、そして世界観の考察とかしてみてくださーい！
...so please watch and listen to it many times, and share your theories!
え、そしてお待たせしました...あ、ちょっと待って、一個言い忘れました！
And sorry to keep you waiting... Ah, wait! I forgot to say one thing!
さっきの曲『管制塔より』24時にリリースもあります！
The song "From the Control Tower" will be released at midnight!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
そしてですね、お待たせしました、新3D！
And now, sorry to keep you waiting, here is my new 3D!
どう？可愛い？可愛い？可愛いー？！
How is it? Is it cute? Cute? So cute?!
はい、もっとね、話すことなく見せたいんだけど、
Yes, I want to show you more without talking, but...
え、ちょっとね、ももこママの、あの、あれ、いつものにすごい近くなったんじゃないかなと思います！
...I think it looks much closer to Momoko-mama's original design!
この後のメン限ライブでね、撮影会もしまして、
I'll be holding a photo shoot during the members-only live stream after this,
さらに細かく見せちゃうので、ぜひメン限ライブも来てください！
...and show it in even more detail, so please come join!
メン限ライブでは、本編で歌えなかったあのゲームの、
During the members-only live stream, I'll also sing everyone's favorite song...
みんなが大好きな曲、キン、キン、キン、キン、キンも歌うよ！お楽しみに！
...from *that* game, "Kin-kin-kin-kin-kin"! Look forward to it!
じゃあ、ひとつだけ新3Dのめっちゃ変わったポイントを教えちゃうと...
So, let me tell you just one major change in this new 3D...
ケモ耳が揺れます！おぉー！可愛いー！はい！
My animal ears twitch! Oh! So cute! Yes!
あ、あと、
And also,
トレンド1位本当にありがとうございます！
thank you so much for the 1st place in trending!
今日無理かなって思ってたんでめちゃめちゃ嬉しかったし、
I thought it'd be impossible today, so I was incredibly happy,
トレンド爆散、なんかすごいいっぱい入ってたみたいで、
and we blew up on trending, seems like so many tags were trending,
本当にありがとう！
thank you so much!
それでは、もうひとつ、
Now then, I have one more...
大切なお知らせです！ドン！
important announcement! Boom!
博衣こより誕生日記念グッズ2026が発売されます！
Hakui Koyori Birthday Commemorative Goods 2026 are going on sale!
早速詳細を見ていきましょう！
Let's check out the details right away!
まず1つ目はこちら！もふこよにもなる！？2WAYブランケット！
First up is this! "Becomes Mofukoyo too!? 2-way Blanket"!
お部屋でゲームを楽しんでいるこよりの描き下ろしイラストです！イラストはもちろん、ももこママ！
It's a newly drawn illustration of Koyori enjoying a game in her room! The illustration is, of course, by Momoko-mama!
これ丸めるともふこよに早変わりして、持ち運びも楽ちんだし、そのままで飾っても可愛いですね！
If you roll this up, it quickly transforms into Mofukoyo! It's easy to carry and cute to display!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ボイスキーホルダー 〜ゲーム実況編〜！
Voice Keyholder - Let's Play Version!
待望のボイスキーホルダーが出ました！こよりの撮り下ろしボイスが入っているもので、
The long-awaited voice keyholder is here! It contains newly recorded voices of Koyori,
今回はライブに合わせて、ゲーム実況中っぽいセリフ、絶叫が6種類入っております！
and to match the live stream, it includes 6 types of let's-play-style lines and screams!
セリフはこよりが考えました！イラストはなもり先生です！
Koyori came up with the lines! The illustration is by Namori-sensei!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
こより監督ぬいぐるみスマホスタンド！
Director Koyori Plushie Smartphone Stand!
あのこより監督がついにぬいぐるみになったよ！可愛い！
That Director Koyori has finally become a plushie! So cute!
そのまま飾るも良し、スマホスタンドにもなるので超便利です！絶対ゲットしてね！
You can just display it, or use it as a smartphone stand, so it's super convenient! Make sure to get one!
最後はこちら！
Last is this!
ゲーム機風カードホルダー！
Game Console-Style Card Holder!
特典のチェキ風ブロマイドとか、ホロカも入れられて、持ち運べちゃうカードホルダーです！
It's a card holder where you can put the bonus instax-style bromide or Holoka cards and carry them around!
中に入っている台紙のイラストはこよちゃんが描き下ろしました！
Koyo-chan drew the illustration for the backing card inside!
ゲーム機風のデザインも、レトロゲームっぽくて可愛くない？
Doesn't the game console-style design look retro and cute?
はい、そして、フルセット特典はこちらです！
Yes, and here is the full set purchase bonus!
ももこママ描き下ろしのチェキ風ブロマイドが付きます！
It comes with an instax-style bromide newly drawn by Momoko-mama!
数量限定版は、直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージ入り！
The limited quantity version includes a hand-signed autograph, foil stamping, and a printed message!
通常版は、箔押しの複製サインとメッセージ入りになってます！...
The regular version includes a foil-stamped printed signature and message!
販売開始は、このあと21時10分にしてあるので、
Sales will start after this at 21:10, so...
皆さん、あの、慌てないで、大丈夫です！10分からなので！
Everyone, um, please don't rush, it's fine! It starts from 10 after!
はい、あの、...
Yes, um...
見てってください！よろしくお願いします！
please check it out! Thank you very much!
さらに、特典ASMRボイスも付きます！
Furthermore, it also comes with a bonus ASMR voice!
毎年恒例の「君の誕生日を逆に祝っちゃうASMRボイス2026ver.」
The annual "Celebrating your birthday instead ASMR voice 2026 ver."!
こちらですね、毎年みんな誕生日まで我慢して聴いて「わーい！」ってなってくれているの、...
For this, I'm so happy every year that everyone waits until their birthday to listen and goes "Yay!"
すごく嬉しく思ってます！ぜひゲットしてください！
I'm really glad! Please be sure to get it!
はい、ということで、...
Yes, so with that...
怒涛のお知らせでしたが、...
it was a flood of announcements, but...
可愛いでしょ？みんなが可愛いって言ってくれてて、こよ嬉しい！
Isn't it cute? Everyone is saying it's cute, and Koyo is so happy!
表情とかもちょっと変わったんですよ！にゃー！あ、これができるようになりました！
My expressions changed a little bit too! Meow! Ah, I can do this now!
あとは、キリッ、いえーい、こんな表情もできるようになりました！面ゲンをお楽しみに！...
Also, look sharp, yay! I can make these expressions now! Look forward to the member-only stream!
ということで、今日は博衣こより生誕ライブ2026ゲームソングライブに見に来てくれてありがとう！...
So, thank you so much for coming to watch Hakui Koyori's Birthday Live 2026 Game Song Live today!
このあとですね、新曲のアニメMV公開と、面ゲンライブ、あれですね、...
After this, we have the release of the new song's animated MV, and the member-only live, right?
アニメMV公開見て、で、10分からグッズ買って、...
Watch the animated MV release, then buy goods from 10 past,
15分から面ゲンライブって感じで、ゆっくり順番に...
and start the member-only live from 15 past, so in order slowly...
いけるようになっているので、慌てず、駆けず、...
we can go through them, so don't rush, don't run...
なんだ、押さず、でよろしくお願いします！...
what is it, don't push, thank you very much!
ということで、今日はちょっと遅れちゃったんだけど、この3Dお披露目して、...
So, although we were a bit late today, I'm glad I could show this 3D...
生誕ライブもできて、大好きなゲームソングいっぱいお披露目できて嬉しかったよ！...
and do the birthday live, and show off so many of my favorite game songs!
みんな本当に見に来てくれてありがとう！...
Thank you all so much for coming to watch!
また会おうね！ありがとう！...
Let's meet again! Thank you!
MV見てね！...
Watch the MV, okay!
バイバイ！...
Bye-bye!